[
    {
        "front": "すむ",
        "back": "住む \nto live",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうみん",
        "back": "住民 \nresident",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ところ",
        "back": "所 \nplace",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいどころ",
        "back": "台所 \nkitchen",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうしょ",
        "back": "住所 \naddress",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "とうきょう",
        "back": "東京 \nTokyo",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうと",
        "back": "京都 \nKyoto",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "みやこ",
        "back": "都 \nmetropolis",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうと",
        "back": "京都 \nKyoto",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅと",
        "back": "首都 \ncapital",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "つごう",
        "back": "都合 \nconvenience, schedule",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふ",
        "back": "府 \nadministrative state",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうとふ",
        "back": "京都府 \nKyoto province",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "やまぐちけん",
        "back": "山口県 \nYamaguchi prefecture",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうとし",
        "back": "京都市 \nKyoto city",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちば",
        "back": "市場 \nmarket",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "く",
        "back": "区 \nward, zone",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きたく",
        "back": "北区 \nKita ward",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "まち",
        "back": "町 \ntown",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょうちょう",
        "back": "町長 \ntown mayor",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "むら",
        "back": "村 \nvillage",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "のうそん",
        "back": "農村 \nfarming village",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "そんちょう",
        "back": "村長 \nvillage head",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "むらびと",
        "back": "村人 \nvillager",
        "chapter": "N4 K1"
    }
]